A Guide to the Correspondence with Horace Liveright 1927-1949
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Correspondence with Horace Liveright 1927-1949
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
8171
This collection consists of 19 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was a gift from Mr. Massey on June 10, 1966
Scope and Content Information
The collection contains correspondence between Faulkner and Liveright of the publishing firm Boni and Liveright regarding the publication of Mosquitoes and the rejected publication of Flags in the Dust, which was eventually published in 1929 by Harcourt Brace and Company under the title Sartoris. A novel by Isadora Duncan is another topic. Also included is one letter, 1949 July 27, from Faulkner to Manuel Komroff.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- William Faulkner to Horace Liveright 1927 Jan 11, 1 p. on 1 l., TLS
- [Horace Liveright] to William Faulkner 1927 Jan 15, 1 p. on 1 l., TL (carbon)
- William Faulkner to Horace Liveright 1927 Feb 18, 1 p. on 1 l., TLS
- William Faulkner to Horace Liveright [1927 Jul 18?], 1 p. on 1 l., TLS
- [Horace Liveright to William Faulkner 1927 Jul 23, 1 p. on 1 l., TL (carbon)
- William Faulkner to Horace Liveright [1927 Jul 27?], 1 p. on 1 l.
- Horace Liveright to William Faulkner 1927 Aug 1, 1 p. on 1 l., TL (carbon)
- William Faulkner to Horace Liveright [1927 Oct 15?], 1 p. on 1 l., TLS
- [Horace Liveright to William Faulkner 1927 Oct 20, 1 p. on 1 l., TL (carbon)
- [Horace Liveright] to William Faulkner 1927 Nov 25, 1 p. on 1 l. each, 2 TL (carbons)
- William Faulkner to Horace Liveright 1927 Nov 30, 1 p. on 1 l., TLS
- Horace Liveright to Arthur, 1 p. on 1 l. 1927 Dec 6, 1 p. on 1 l., AN
- [Horace Liveright] to William Faulkner 1927 Dec 10, 1 p. on 1 l., TL (carbon)
- [Horace Liveright] to William Faulkner 1928 Feb 27, 1 p. on 1 l., TL (carbon)
- William Faulkner to Horace Liveright [1928 Mar 1?], 1 p. on 1 l., TLS
- [Horace Liveright] to William Faulkner 1928 Mar 12, 1 p. on 1 l., TL
- William Faulkner to Horace Liveright [1928?], 1 p. on 1 l., TLS
- "Bill" [Faulkner] to Manuel [Komroff?] 1949 Jul 27, 1 p. on 1 l., TLS